

CONTACTS

Republic of Belarus, Brest tel. +375 (29) 723 00 90 email: victor.chizh@mail.ru telegram: t.me/ViktorChizh

github.com/ViktorChizh
linkedin.com/in/ViktorChizh
codewars.com/users/ViktorChizh

EDUCATION

IT-INCUBATOR Vocational training Typescript, React, Redax, Redux-Toolkit, RTK-query, Redux-Saga, Jest, Storybook, Postman, Styled Components, RadixUI, etc.

Nov. 2023 - present

Educational center "Leader"

Python, Django

Oct. 2022 - Feb. 2023

Educational center "Leader"

HTML, CSS, JavaScript Jan. 2022 - Sep. 2022

Belarusian National Technical University

Instrumentation

GPA: cum laude Sep. 1992 - Jun. 1997

ONLINE COURSES

Front End Development Libraries freeCodeCamp Oct. 2023

Responsive Web Design

<u>freeCodeCamp</u> Oct. 2023

<u>JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures</u> <u>freeCodeCamp</u> Sep. 2023

LANGUAGES

Russian - native

English - Pre-Intermediate A2 (in progress)

VIKTOR CHIZH

ABOUT ME

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Hi, I am a Front-end developer with +2 year of development experience (including six months of commercial experience) in creating SPA.

I work with technologies such as React, TypeScript, Redux, Redux Toolkit, RTK-query, Redux-Saga and other related libraries.

Constantly improving my skills and I want to expand them with new technologies like Angular, Vue.js, React Native, Next.js, GraphQL and others. My goal is to eventually become a Full-stack developer.

In my free time, I enjoy solving problems on Codewars and learning about new technologies, also improve my English level.

I am always open to new opportunities and would be happy to chat and consider your proposals. Additional information in <u>Portfolio</u> or in <u>LinkedIn</u>.

WORK EXPERIENCES

☑ IT-incubator

Nov. 2023 - present

Vocational training, where I consolidate my knowledge and fill existing gaps in it. The training process is as close as possible to real production.

Projects: Flash cards, TodoLIst, Social network

Key Responsibilities:

- Team development using Git.
- Create custom hooks and reusable components.
- Architectural solutions for projects (layering UI, BLL, DAL, Server).
- Full auth flow with registration, login, recover password.
- Form processing and validation.
- Create private routes and redirecting. Working with the server using Ajax. (CRUD operations and data processing with RESTful).
- Pagination, search, filter and sorting features. Image uploading.
- Refactoring to eliminate code duplication, bug fixing.
- Covering applications with tests using Jest.
- Creating reusable utility functions.
- Creating various modal windows.
- Improving performance and optimization.

Stack: React, TypeScript, Redux Toolkit, RTK-query, React Hook Form, Formik, React-routerdom, Axios, MaterialUI, RadixUI, Storybook, Jest, Git.

Relotech Solution

Jun. 2023 - Dec. 2023

Commercial internship as a front-end developer on a Relocate project (aggregator of statistical data about countries of the world).

The work was carried out:

- a full-stack team of 15 people (back-end, front-end, UI/UX, QA, DevOps engineer, BA, PM)
- according to the Agile methodology with daily sprints
- using a task-tracker ClickUp

Stack: Next.js, MobX, React, React-router, React DOM, HTML, SCSS, Git

SKILLS HTML CSS, SCSS, SASS JavaScript TypeScript React Next.js MobX Redux, Redux Toolkit, RTK-query, Redux-Saga Jest Git Styled Components Bootstrap MaterialUl RadixUl

🗸 Storybook 🗸 Postman 🗸 Python 📞 Django 🗸 SQL 🗸 ect.